seositecheckup.com 2018-12-26

# Private Policy | SeoSiteCheckup.com

##### 1\. WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This policy covers how SEO Site Checkup treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of SEO Site Checkup products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SEO Site Checkup does not own or control, or to people that SEO Site Checkup does not employ or manage. 

##### 2\. THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

SEO Site Checkup collects personally identifiable information only upon user consent. The information is normally gathered through our surveys, newsletters, or other services we offer to users. Information collected may include, but are not exclusive to names, addresses, email address, educational history, and phone numbers of users of SEO Site Checkup. 

SEO Site Checkup features profiles of how-to ebooks. Anonymous information is collected in the form of site and page traffic performance which include geographic and demographic information. 

##### 3\. HOW PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE USED

Personal information can be used to customize content and enhance user experience. Site and page statistical information is used to measure site popularity and usage. Users who have shared information may receive newsletters, site announcements, or promotional materials from public schools and other site partners. Users can always contact our site (information@seositecheckup.com) and request to remove their information from all distribution lists. 

##### 4\. HOW PRIVATE INFORMATION IS PROTECTED, CHANGED AND UPDATED.

All personal information is stored on our secure servers only accessible by SEO Site Checkup employees. Under no circumstance is personal identifiable information released to the public or site partners without explicit consent of our users.

Account information and deletion of personal identifiable information will be executed upon user request.
